library my_globals.globals;
import 'package:flutter_apps/question_set.dart';

List<QuestionSet> questionBank = [
    QuestionSet(question:'Day',answer: 'Night'),
    QuestionSet(question:'Black',answer: 'White'),
    QuestionSet(question:'Good',answer: 'Bad'),
    QuestionSet(question:'Ugly',answer: 'Beautiful'),
    QuestionSet(question:'Cricket',answer: 'Baseball'),
    QuestionSet(question:'Morning',answer: 'Evening'),
    QuestionSet(question:'Here',answer: 'There'),
    QuestionSet(question:'Up',answer: 'Down'),
    QuestionSet(question:'Cat',answer: 'Dog'),
    QuestionSet(question:'Far',answer: 'Near'),
];